fabkids.com 2017-03-30

# Privacy Policy | FabKids

This Privacy Policy was last updated on Sep 20, 2016.

### Our Policy

Your privacy is very important to us. This privacy policy addresses how TechStyle, Inc. (f/k/a Just Fabulous, Inc.), and its subsidiary Personal Retailing, Inc. (d/b/a FabKids) and affiliated brands (collectively, "FabKids") collect and use information you provide. By visiting www.fabkids.com (this "Site"), and providing your information to us, you agree to accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

### What Information Is Collected

We group the collection of user information into two categories: personal, which is information identifiable to a specific member, and aggregate, which is general demographic information that does not identify any individual member. Personal information may include your name, email address, mailing address, credit card information and phone number. We may also collect certain demographic information such as your Site preferences, sizes, age, gender, geographical location, language, time zone, income and education (some of the information we ask for may be optional). FabKids may use or disclose aggregate information for any purpose.

### How We Use Your Information

We collect personal information to make our services related to this Site (the "Services") more rewarding for you to use, including billing, shipping and tracking your orders. If we have any questions or concerns regarding your order, we may use this information to contact you. We also use this information for internal purposes, such as studying our customers' preferences and improving customer experience on the Site. We may also use your information to contact you for promotional purposes and provide customer service to you. If you enter into a sweepstakes, contest or similar promotion, we may use the information you provide to administer those activities. We may combine information about you with information from other sources in order to improve the quality of our Services.

We also receive and store certain personally non-identifiable information, which is collected passively using various technologies, and cannot presently be used to specifically identify you. This Site may use such information and pool it with other information to track, for example, the total number of visitors to our Site, the number of visitors to each page of our Site, the domain names of our visitors' Internet service providers, and how our users use and interact with the Services. Also, in an ongoing effort to better understand and serve you, we often conduct research on customer demographics, interests and behavior based on the personal and other information provided to us. This research may be compiled and analyzed on an aggregate basis. We may share this non-identifiable and aggregate data with affiliates, agents and business partners, but this type of non-identifiable and aggregate information does not identify you personally. We may also disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe our Services to current and prospective business partners, and to other third parties for other lawful purposes.

### How Is This Information Shared

There are certain circumstances in which we may share your personal information with certain third parties without further notice to you, as set forth below:  

  * We may share information about you with trusted third parties in order to improve your customer experience. These third parties may contact you about products, services or promotions you may be interested in, or to otherwise improve your customer experience with this Site.
  * We may share information about you, such as your name, address, email address, as well as a record of any transactions you conduct on our website or offline with us via our third-party advertising partners and its service providers, in order to deliver to you banner advertisements and other advertising tailored to your interests when you visit certain websites. Our advertising partners will make the data we provide to it anonymous. To learn more about the use of this information or to make choices about receiving personalized advertising provided by third parties, please visit the Network Advertising Initiative by clicking here (<https://www.networkadvertising.org/choices>).
  * As we develop our business, we might sell or buy businesses or assets. In the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution or similar event, your information may be part of the transferred assets.
  * When we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect the rights, property and safety of FabKids, its users or the public.
  * As required by law, to comply with a judicial proceeding or court order, to exercise our rights, or to defend against any claims.

### Cookies and Web Beacons

This Site uses cookies and web beacons to gather aggregated, non-personally identifiable information in order to help us better understand user behavior, tell us which parts of this Site users have visited, and facilitate and measure the effectiveness of advertisements and web searches. Such information may be shared with trusted third parties but the information will not personally identify you. To the extent that Internet Protocol (IP) addresses or similar identifiers are considered personal information by local law, we also treat these identifiers as personal information. Similarly, to the extent that non-personal information is combined with personal information, we treat the combined information as personal information. As we develop this Site, we may gather additional information from you through the use of other technologies.

### Cookies

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies to collect anonymous information about how you use this Site by setting and accessing cookies on your computer. These cookies track information such as how often you visit our Site, what pages you view, and where you go after you leave our Site. The cookies are not connected to your personal information. We recommend that you leave cookies turned on because they allow you to take advantage of some of this Site's features.

### Web Beacons

Web beacons, or clear gifs, are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user's computer hard drive, web beacons are embedded invisibly on web pages. Web beacons help us better manage content on our Site by informing us what content is effective. We do not tie the information gathered by web beacons to your personal information.

### Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you provide sensitive information (such as a credit card number), we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the absolute security of such information. If you have any questions about security on our Site, please contact us as indicated below.

### Opting Out

We may occasionally send you newsletters and emails regarding special offers, promotions, features and/or product updates. We may also communicate with you on behalf of third parties about special offers, promotions, features and/or product updates we think may be of interest to you, or you may have opted-in to receive newsletters or special promotions from one of our trusted third party providers. If you decide you do not wish to receive these communications, you may opt-out by clicking the unsubscribe link or by following the instructions included in the communication. Note however that as user of the Services you cannot opt-out of some administrative communications that are reasonably necessary to the Services, such as billing or service notifications. You may also opt-out of certain targeted advertising by visiting <https://www.networkadvertising.org/choices>.

### Links to Other Sites

This Site may contain links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by us. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Site. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our Site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy does not cover any information that you disclose to such sites or that they may collect. The privacy policies of these other sites may be significantly different from this Privacy Policy. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites and cannot guarantee the security of any of your personal information collected there. This Site may enable you to post comments, reviews and other information on publicly available areas of this Site. Any information you post in these areas of this Site will be available to all of our users, so please use caution in disclosing any personal information when you post such comments, reviews or other information.

### Facebook

You can log in to your account using your Facebook account, or utilize your Facebook account to access and use the social features on this Site. In doing so, Facebook will ask your permission to share certain information from your Facebook account with this Site. This may include your first name, last name, gender, profile picture, list of friends, a link to your Facebook profile, likes, and other data that is part of your or your friends' Facebook profile(s). This information is collected by Facebook and is provided to us under the terms of Facebook's Privacy Policy. You can control the information that we receive from Facebook using the privacy settings in your Facebook account. If you use your Facebook account to access and use the social features on this Site, your Facebook user name and your Facebook profile picture will be shared with other users of this Site. Further, other users of this Site may be able to view your profile and shopping activity on this Site.

You may choose to share your shopping activity on this Site with your friends on Facebook. A subset of your user activity on this Site, including your likes, purchases, wishlists and friends will automatically be shared to both your friends on Facebook and with your Facebook friends on this Site. Additionally, such activity will be visible to users on this Site who have a Facebook account but who might not be your friend on Facebook. The information you choose to share with your Facebook friends will be attributed to your Facebook account that was used to access this Site. Facebook's use of such information and any information it collects from your use of Facebook is governed by Facebook's Privacy Policy. FabKids has no liability or responsibility for the privacy practices or other actions of Facebook that may be enabled within use of this Site. The use of information on this Site is governed by this Site's Privacy Policy. You understand and acknowledge that you have read and are familiar with this Site's Privacy Policy and Facebook's Privacy Policy. If you do not wish to share your activity on this Site with your friends on Facebook, you may adjust your sharing settings on this Site at any time to disable such sharing. You understand and acknowledge that if you adjust your settings to disable such sharing on Facebook, such activity may continue to be publicly available to other users on this Site, including users with Facebook accounts.

### Updating or Deleting Your Online Account Information

You may update or correct your online account information at any time by logging into your account and navigating to the "My Account" page or by contacting us. You can also contact us by phone if you wish to deactivate your account, but note that we may retain certain information as required by law or for legitimate business purposes. We may also retain cached or archived copies of information about you for a certain period of time.

### Children Under 13

Children under 13 may view this Site, but they cannot make a purchase or provide any personal information. This Site is not designed for children and we do not wish to collect personal information from children under 13. If you register with us and we discover that you are under 13, we will delete your account. You must be 18 or over to purchase any products from this Site. If a child under the age of 13 has provided us with personally identifiable information online, we ask that a parent or guardian contact us.

### Exclusion to This Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy shall not apply to any unsolicited information you provide to FabKids through this Site or through any other means. This includes, but is not limited to, information posted to any public areas of the Site, such as review sections and forums (collectively, "Public Areas"), any ideas for new products or modifications to existing products, and other unsolicited submissions (collectively, "Unsolicited Information"). All Unsolicited Information shall be deemed to be non-confidential and FabKids shall be free to reproduce, use, disclose, distribute and exploit such Unsolicited Information without limitation or attribution.

### California Residents

If you are a California resident and have an established business relationship with us, you can request a notice disclosing the categories of personal information we have shared with third parties, for the third parties' direct marketing purposes, during the preceding calendar year. To request a notice, please submit your request to Personal Retailing, Inc. (FabKids), Attn: Legal Department, California Shine the Light Inquiry, 800 Apollo Drive, El Segundo, CA 90245.

### EU-US Privacy Shield Program

FabKids complies with the EU-US Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use and retention of personal information from European Union member countries. FabKids has certified that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles of Notice, Choice, Accountability for Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity and Purpose Limitation, Access, and Recourse, Enforcement and Liability. If there is any conflict between the policies in this Privacy Policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification page, please visit [https://www.privacyshield.gov/welcome](https://www.privacyshield.gov/welcome.).

### Types of Data Collected Under the EU-US Privacy Shield

Personal data such as your name, email address, mailing address, credit card information, phone number and IP address are collected. This personal data is used for the following purposes: to process and fulfill orders, communicate with you about orders, any FabKids service, marketing and sales, internal research, and compliance with federal, state and local laws and regulations. FabKids also collects aggregate data such as your Site preferences, sizes, age, gender, geographical location, language, time zone, income and education. This aggregate data is used for the following purposes: marketing and sales activities, to optimize shopping experience and types of goods sold, internal research, partnerships or agreements with affiliates, agents and business partners, and to describe our Services to current and prospective business partners.

ShoeDazzle.com, Inc. (d/b/a ShoeDazzle) collects the following types of personal data: name, email address, mailing address, credit card information, phone number and IP address. The following aggregate data may also be collected: Site preferences, age, gender, geographical location, language, time zone, income and education.

TechStyle, Inc. (f/k/a Just Fabulous, Inc.) (d/b/a JustFab) collects the following types of personal data: name, email address, mailing address, credit card information, phone number and IP address. The following aggregate data may also be collected: Site preferences, age, gender, geographical location, language, time zone, income and education.

Fabletics LLC (d/b/a Fabletics and FL2) collects the following types of personal data: name, email address, mailing address, credit card information, phone number and IP address. The following aggregate data may also be collected: Site preferences, age, gender, geographical location, language, time zone, income and education.

### Who We Share Information With Under the EU-US Privacy Shield

FabKids may disclose personal and non-personally identifiable aggregate data with affiliates, subsidiaries, business partners, advertisers and vendors. The purpose for disclosure to affiliates, subsidiaries and business partners is to improve customer experience, for internal research and marketing and sales purposes. We may share information with advertisers and vendors to comply with lawful agreements and for advertising purposes. FabKids retains potential liability in cases of onward transfer of information to third parties.

FabKids may also be required to disclose personal information in response to a lawful request by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

Individuals will be notified by FabKids in the event it uses or discloses information for a purpose other than that for which the information was originally collected or discloses information to a non-agent third party. Notice may take a variety of forms, including through amendments or modifications to this Privacy Policy.

### Accessing and Updating Your Personal Information

You have the right to access, correct or delete personal data which has been provided to FabKids. At any time, you may update or correct your online account information by logging into your account and navigating to the "My Account" page or by contacting us. You may also delete your personal data by contacting us to deactivate your account, but note that we may retain certain information as required by law or for legitimate business purposes. We may also retain cached or archived copies of information about you for a certain period of time.

If you do not want FabKids to use or disclose your information or provide your information to third parties for marketing and sales purposes, please contact FabKids at the address provided below under “Inquiries or Complaints Regarding the EU-US Privacy Shield Program”. If you have already received a non-administrative communication that you did not wish to receive, you may opt-out by clicking the unsubscribe link or by following the instructions included in the communication.

### Inquiries or Complaints Regarding the EU-US Privacy Shield Program

In compliance with the EU-US Privacy Shield Principles, FabKids commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. European Union individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding this Privacy Policy should first contact FabKids at:

JustFab (UK), Ltd.  
Attn: Legal Department/Privacy  
Antony Stokes, VP & International General Counsel  
8-10 Dryden Street, First Floor  
London, WC2E9NA  
United Kingdom  

FabKids has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the EU-US Privacy Shield Principles BBB EU PRIVACY SHIELD, a non-profit alternative dispute resolution provider located in the United States and operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed, please visit [www.bbb.org/EU-privacy-shield/for-eu-consumers/](https://www.bbb.org/EU-privacy-shield/for-eu-consumers/) for more information and to file a complaint. There is no charge to consumers for calling or using this independent dispute resolution mechanism.

Under certain limited conditions, European Union individuals may be able to invoke binding arbitration before the Privacy Shield Panel to be created by the U.S. Department of Commerce and the European Commission.

FabKids is subject to the jurisdiction and investigatory and enforcement powers of the Federal Trade Commission (FTC).

### Amendments or Modifications to this Policy

We reserve the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time without prior notice. Notice of any change will be posted on this Site. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of the Site after any changes or revisions to this Privacy Policy shall indicate your agreement with the terms of such revised Privacy Policy.

### Contact Us

If you have any questions regarding the use of our site or privacy policy, please contact us at:

Personal Retailing, Inc. (FabKids)  
Attn: Legal Department/Privacy  
800 Apollo Drive  
El Segundo, CA 90245  
Or 1-866-337-0906
